Hey there player number one, the action in the market is
tremendous, Nifty is up 222 points, the native
and definition of tom and I will
click around destination lover point two one,
you will find many festival fans, Saif, one is win
for textile event, global market, death,
life and friends, the results have come out good, whatever
numbers were reported yesterday,
except Rajesh, everyone has performed well
and we will focus on such a company, while
ICICI Lombard and I will
present the numbers before you, this quarter has actually
proved to be strong for the company, here
we have seen an increase of 80 percent in profitability
and also there has been a
growth of up to 30 percent in cross premium,
underwriting classification has appeared to be more sour,
more details film
Ayesha, co-op and shifting of the company Bhopal
Balachandran Hands Gopal, welcome,
very strong figures have been seen on housing from sugar,
net profit is big due to which there has been
good growth in them, basically, Prem,
so I was noticing
this time that there has been a lot of improvement in your health business  If you have
got it, then is
this where the maximum demand
seems to be generated and are you aggressive in
this business?
Good morning, bank robbery, this is a very good
question. If you look at our
growth from this number,
we have been focusing a lot on three segments.
One is motor insurance. Where also
tell me about your anger, this job agro, in that
motor insurance people, the
growth of the industry has also been almost at chip
level. If you talk about the feel, what
you said in the mails is absolutely correct.
Our protest which I have been on overall health issues is
30 percent. If you
look at it in comparison to the industry, then the
growth of the industry has been approximately what
percent. So in the sense of
romance, now we have
also written on the Inspiration Hotel Broadway production line, fire
engineering liability, dead buffalo, which is the
distance from the segment,
we have written on that, well, angry, and
oil, more vitamin barriers, immersed
electrons, motive and across the world
and a commercial line, Kuru
going  Forward the rough is it came by train
that will remain intact and here
Riteshvar Group business because I am
remembering where better margin
melt
if you do it in two parts
last 90 days were fighting
subscribe
thank you
Robert text on health insurance premium
bound range of 20%
soft drinks strength and confidence please read
flight ingredients see acid is where
our office focus has been and again and last
nine to 10 inches we are doing office on distribution
and detailed explanation and on
this if you look at we and last
not period if almost lost wards from
oppression particularly for retail health is
institution for employers of snow
white and deputy superintendent and
market and kids moral and ethical helper
shooting of pensioners union solidarity
questions are doing job investment by cutting forward
and there is a special edition nutritious little
in it we definitely
expect the group-2 salary and factor
Drip waters corporate is lighting candles
that Mirwaiz increase in Indian Revenue
Service will come on top of the volume of the
policies price increase SIM labels and
last year B.Com scientific udaya next
couple of protest for details delivery
hospital and placed
in coffins I would like to say that going forward
with this coming back to decide number plate will be
able to decide what kind of demand will be
arrested they should avoid
eating
eggs
subscribe this subscribe our
market has been
20000 se zor par and here also increase the
voice kids pe anwar shoot kam hi
underwriting side there it always maintain at all
stags and dumb you will
think a lot after we are in it this to increase in the
portfolio raises award demand in terms
of vesting plan mode setting
different segments batting motor insurance are having different
levels of maturity if we
talk about private car you will go through the wars
more lead researcher
idusing kevin  Order backlog this bulk pack
net last two years at same place and
contributed to multiple threats
tags page 9 tags page 10 expecting to get much
better in the second half of the year when it comes to
private tax if you
talk about Tubelight then three still think should not
working out of the day
expectation letter two wheeler shoot come back to
normal senior leaders in the last several
years when they see in factory decline in the
number of wisdom quote told you will be amazed
as proof and 15 clear commercial banks that
tractor ek baat aisi hai jahan par dard
do tasbeer points scientist if he
talks about this number thank you have been focusing
on oct president deletes tweet call two
wheeler and commercial banks in the current
affair also send voice note to increase mix
commission makers who were earlier in this sentiment
improved t and you all voters lists
commissionerate contribution the number  Also believe that
will guide 12345 per cent to a gross
elements our focus should be Tubelight
prevent two-wheeler NCB in aggregate at
this point of time looking at the
moment moment of bali pure giving life
line also market thank you very much or
central mileage for taking out time and
wishing you all the best primary water
system